Sean Connery is James Bond 007
Never Say Never Again is a adventure, action,
thriller film directed by Irvin Kershner.
James Bond returns as the secret agent 007 to
battle the evil organization SPECTRE.
Bond must defeat Largo, who has stolen two atomic
warheads for nuclear blackmail.
But Bond has an ally in Largo's girlfriend, the willowy
Domino, who falls for Bond and seeks revenge.
James Bond, played by Sean Connery.
Maximilian Largo, played by Klaus Maria Brandauer.
Ernst Stavro Blofeld, played by Max von Sydow.
Fatima Blush, played by Barbara Carrera.
Domino Petachi, played by Kim Basinger.
Felix Leiter, played by Bernie Casey.
Never Say Never Again is a 1983 spy film directed by Irvin Kershner.
The film is based on the 1961 James Bond novel Thunderball by Ian Fleming, which in turn was
based on an original story by Kevin McClory, Jack Whittingham, and Fleming.
The novel had been previously adapted as the 1965 film Thunderball.
Never Say Never Again is the second and most recent James Bond film not to be produced by Eon Productions (the usual
producer of the Bond series) but instead by Jack Schwartzman's Taliafilm, and was distributed by Warner Bros.
The film was executive produced by Kevin McClory, one of the
original writers of the Thunderball storyline.
McClory had retained the filming rights of the novel
following a long legal battle dating from the 1960s.
Sean Connery played the role of Bond for the seventh and final time, marking his
return to the character twelve years after Diamonds Are Forever (1971).
The film's title is a reference to Connery's reported declaration
in 1971 that he would "never again" play that role.
As Connery was 52 at the time of filming, the script makes frequent reference to Bond as aging and past his
prime – although Connery was three years younger than his Eon Productions replacement, Roger Moore.
The storyline features Bond being reluctantly brought back into action to
investigate the theft of two nuclear weapons by SPECTRE.
Filming locations included France, Spain, the Bahamas,
and Elstree Studios in the United Kingdom.
Never Say Never Again was released by Warner Bros.
on 7 October 1983, and opened to positive reviews, with critics praising
the cast's performances and Connery's return to the role.
The film grossed $160 million at the box office, making it a commercial success, although it
earned less overall than the Eon-produced Octopussy, released earlier the same year.
Retrospective reception to Never Say Never Again has been mixed, and it is
considered by several critics to be one of the weaker Bond films.
The film explores themes of video game, spy, bahamas, stealing, scuba diving.
The tone is intense.